Guide to the Lewis Carroll Society of North America Archive, 1974-2015 MSS.148
Fales Library and Special Collections
Lewis Carroll Society of North America Archives
circa 1972-2015
Fales Library and Special Collections
Lewis Carroll Society of North America
MSS.148
4.75 Linear Feet in 7 boxes
The Lewis Carroll Society of North America (LCSNA) is an organization dedicated to celebrating the works of Lewis Carroll. The collection is composed of documents and correspondence related to the activities of the Society, including publications and meetings.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical / Historical
The Lewis Carroll Society of North America (LCSNA) was established in by Stan Marx in 1974. LCSNA is a not-for-profit organization dedicated to "furthering Carroll studies, increasing accessibility of research materials, and maintaining public awareness of Carroll's contribution to society." The organization meets twice a year, and has an active publications program.
Scope and Contents
The Lewis Carroll Society of North America (LCSNA) Archive contains documents that date between 1972 through 2015 and are related to all aspects of LCSNA's activities. Materials includes a copy of LCSNA's Constitution, legal documents, financial statements, meeting minutes, correspondence among Society members (both letters and cards), publication contracts, membership lists, a copy of the Members' Opinion and Interest survey from 2007, a few Alice's Adventures in Wonderland pins, and copies of the Society newsletter "The Knight Letter."
Arrangement
The materials are arranged at the collection-level by material type, project, and publication, and each series is either organized alphabetically or chronologically. Pre-processing of the collection was done by the Lewis Carroll Society of North America (LCSNA). Materials from the 2012 remained in the order in which they were received from the donor and added, using the previously-established arrangement scheme, to Series I: Constitution and Organic Documents, Series II: Publications, Series III: Membership Records, and Series VII: Miscellaneous.
Materials from the 2016 accretion remained in the order in which they were received from the donor and were added to the collection as a separate series.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll (MSS 057)
Separated Materials
Printed books were separated from the archive and individually catalogued. They are accessible through BobCat and include the following:
Feeding the Mind: A Centenary Celebration of Lewis Carroll's Visit to Alfreton in 1884. Edited by Selwyn Goodacre. Carroll Studies No. 7, 1984.
The Hunting of the Snark, illustrated by Barry Moser. Carroll Studies no.7, 1983
The Hunting of the Snark, illustrated by Jonathon Dixon. Deluxe Edition, 1992.
The Hunting of the Snark, illustrated by Jonathon Dixon. Regular Edition, 1992.
In Memoriam-- Charles Lutwidge Dodgson, 1832-1898, edited by August Imholtz Jr. and Charlie Lovett, 1998.
Lewis Carroll: an Annotated Bibliography 1960-1977, edited by Edward Guiliano, 1977.
Lewis Carroll: an Annotated Bibliography for 1974, edited by Edward Guiliano. Carroll Studies no.1, 1974.
Lewis Carroll and the Kitchins, edited by Morton M. Cohen. Carroll Studies no.4, 1980.
Lewis Carroll at Texas, Carroll Studies no. 8, 1985
Lewis Carroll in the Popular Culture, edited by Byron Sewell, 1976.
Lewis Carroll's Library, edited by Jeffrey Stern. Carroll Studies no.5, 1981.
The Mathematical Pamphlets of Charles Lutwidge Dodgson and Related Pieces, edited by Francine Ables, 1994.
The Political Pamphlets of Charles Lutwidge Dodgson and Related Pieces: A Mathematical Approach, edited by Francine Ables, 2001.
Proceedings of the 2nd International Lewis Carroll Conference, edited by Charles Lovett, 1994.
Soaring with the Dodo, edited by Edward Guiliano, 1982.
Thimbles and Hope, edited by August A. Imholtz, Jr, 1999.
The Wasp in a Wig, limited deluxe edition, red cloth boards, 1977.
The Wasp in a Wig. Carroll Studies no. 2, 1977.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Lewis Carroll Society of North America (LCSNA) Archive was initially donated to the Fales Library in March 2003. An accretion was received from LCSNA in November of 2012, and a second accretion was donated by LCSNA member August Imholtz in 2014. In July 2016, an accretion of material was once again received by August Imholtz; the accession number associated with this gift is 2016.052.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audio materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
Correspondence.; Clippings (information artifacts); Photographs.; Printed ephemera.; Contracts; Financial records; Audiocassettes.; Magazines (Periodicals); Lovett, Charles C.; Guiliano, Edward; Imholtz, Clare; Carroll, Lewis, 1832-1898; Carroll, Lewis, 1832-1898 -- Criticism and interpretation; Carroll, Lewis, 1832-1898 -- Congresses; Lewis Carroll Society of North America -- Periodicals; Lewis Carroll Society of North America -- Anniversaries; Lewis Carroll Society of North America -- History
- Series I: Constitution and Organic Documents
  Scope and Contents note
  Documents relating to the formal establishment of the LCSNA
  - Constitution Draft, President's correspondence regarding drafts, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution revisions, drafts and correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Circular letters and correspondence regarding the establishment of the LCSNA, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Legal incorporation papers and related correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Financial correspondence- includes tax exemption information and application for a Library of Congress number, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Series II: Publications
  Books and other printed works produced by the LCSNA. Includes galley proofs, newsletters, and "keepsakes", pamphlets and bookmarks distributed to members at LCSNA meetings.
  - Subseries A: Books
    Separated Materials
    See separated materials note for the complete listing of books contained in this collection.
    - Gathered signatures for "The Pamphlets of Lewis Carroll", 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Proofs of "Russian Journal, Vol.2", includes photographs, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - "Lewis Carroll's Library", galley proof, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - "Lewis Carroll Observed", galley proof, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - "The Hunting of the Snark", galley proof, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Lewis Carroll, and Annotated Bibliography for 1974", galley proof (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: "The Knight Letter"
    - The Knight Letter, n. 1-5, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 6-13, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 14-17, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 18-23, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 24-30, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 31-39, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 40-48, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 49-53, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 54-58, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 59-65, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 66-70, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The Knight Letter, n. 71, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Subseries C: Keepsakes
    - Princeton, NJ- bookmarks, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Morgan Library, NY NY- invitations and programs, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Princeton, NJ- invitations to 10th Anniversary celebration, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Winston-Salem, NC- "Alice in North Carroll-ina", schedule and exhibition notes, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Morgan Library, NY NY- bookmarks, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Toronto, Canada- Wood engraving on hand-made paper of "The Garden of Live Flowers", 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Beltsville, MD- Microfiche- "The Hunting of the Snark"., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Princeton, NJ- "Stan Marx Memorial"- oversize pamphlet., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Austin, TX- 'Enough of a Muchness" and "Warren Weaver"- pamphlets., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Subseries D: "The Herald"- LCSNA West Coast Chapter Newsletter
    Irregular newsletter of the West Coast Chapter- includes mailing list for CA branch and related correspondence
    - The Herald- LCSNA West Coast Chapter newsletter, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Subseries E: Morton N. Cohen Publication Trust
    Documents relating to establishment of the Trust.
    - Morton N. Cohen Publication Trust, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Subseries F: Publication Contracts and Documents
    Includes publication contracts for LCSNA books and pamphlets, and correspondence with the Carroll estate
    - Publication contracts and documents, 1976-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Publication contracts and documents, 1976-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Subseries G: LCSNA 25th Anniversary Publication
    Includes proof pages of "Thimbles and Hope", plus correspondence from members and officers regarding their involvement with LCSNA
    - LCSNA 25th Anniversary Publication, 1974-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - LCSNA 25th Anniversary Publication, 1974-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - LCSNA 25th Anniversary Publication, 1974-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Series III: Membership Records
  Documentation of LCSNA membership, from 1974-2000, and correspondence between LCSNA officers, LCSNA members, prospective members, and the public.
  - Subseries A: Membership Lists
    Official membership lists prepared by the Secretaries of LCSNA
    - Membership Lists, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Membership Lists, 1973-1989, 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Membership Lists, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Membership Lists, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Subseries B: Membership Cards
    Membership roster on index cards, used by Secretaries to prepare membership lists in the early years of LCSNA. First 7 folders are in random order, and the last 5 are arranged alphabetically.
    - Membership Cards, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Membership Cards, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Membership Cards, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Membership Cards, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Membership Cards, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Membership Cards, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Membership Cards, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Membership Cards A-D, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Membership Cards E-H, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Membership Cards I-M, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Membership Cards N-S, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Membership Cards T-Z, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Subseries C: Samples of Secretary-Membership Correspondence
    Examples of LCSNA interaction with members and non-members, 1976-1985.
    - Members-Secretary Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Members-Secretary Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Members-Secretary Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Members-Secretary Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Members-Secretary Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Members-Secretary Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Members-Secretary Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Members-Secretary Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Membership Opinion and Interests Survey Forms
    Circulated in 1991, this was a general survey regarding LCSNA membership interests. Results were summarized in the 1992 issues of "The Knight Letter".
    - Membership Survey Responses, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Membership Survey Responses, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Series IV: General Meeting Records
  Files contain copies of official meeting notices and programs, correspondence with speakers and host sites, and all other correspondence relating to general meeting organization and preparation. Some folders in the series are in the Oversize box, please see Oversize container list for details.
  - December 7, 1974- Gotham Book Mart, New York NY (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - May 3, 1975- Wye Plantation, MD, and Exhibit at Library of Congress, Washington, DC (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - November 1, 1975- Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - November 6, 1976- Graduate Center, City University of New York, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - November 5, 1977- University of Maryland, Baltimore County, MD (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - May 13, 1978- Rosenbach Foundation and Library, Philadelphia, PA (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - May 19, 1979- Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - October 20, 1979- Canady Library, Bryn Mawr College, Bryn Mawr, PA (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - May 17, 1980- Joseph I. Lubin House, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - May 8, 1981- Houghton Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - January 30, 1982- Pierpont Morgan Library New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - July 26-31,1982- Christ Church, Oxford, England (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - December 11,1982- New York Public Library, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sesquicentennial Materials and Meetings, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - May 28, 1983- Folger Shakespeare Library, Washington, DC (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - October 29, 1983- Firestone Library, Princeton University, Princeton, NJ (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - April 7, 1984- Gleason Library, University of San Francisco, San Francisco, CA (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - November 17, 1984- Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - April 20, 1985- Newberry Library, Chicago, IL (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - November 9, 1985- Harry Ransom Humanities Research Center, University of Texas at Austin, TX (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - April 26, 1986- Donnell Library, New York Public Library, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - November 15, 1986- Boston Public Library, Boston, MA (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - April 25, 1987- Enoch Pratt Library, Baltimore, MD (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - October 24, 1987- Century Club, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - May 15, 1988- Huntington Library, San Marino, CA (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - October 15, 1988- Free Library of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, PA (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - May 5-7, 1989- Forsythe County Library and home of Charles and Stephanie Lovett, Winston-Salem, NC (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - October 21, 1989- Pierpont Morgan Library, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - May 12, 1990- Toronto Public Library, Toronto, Canada (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - October 20, 1990- Enoch Pratt Library, Baltimore, MD (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - April 20, 1991- Grolier Club, New York, NY (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - October 5, 1991- Wheaton Regional Library, Silver Spring, MD, and the homes of David and Maxine Shaefer, August and Clare Imholtz, and Alan and Alison Tannenbaum, Silver Spring, Beltsville, and Washington Grove, MD (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - May 2, 1992- Fales Library, Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University, New York, NY (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - October 17, 1992- Gleason Library, University of San Francisco, San Francisco, CA (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - May 15, 1993- New York Public Library, New York, NY (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - November 20, 1993- Houghton Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - June 9-12, 1994- Graylyn Conference Center, Wake Forest University, Winston-Salem, NC (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - November 12, 1994- Princeton University, Princeton, NJ (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - October 28, 1995- Home of Jon and Ginny Lindseth, Hunting Valley, OH, and The Rowfant Club, Cleveland, OH (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - April 27, 1996- Rosenbach Museum and Library, Philadelphia, PA, and Germantown Theatre and Kitty Minehart's Home, Germantown, PA (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - November 9, 1996- Brown University, Providence, RI (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - April 19, 1997- Fales Library, Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University, New York, NY (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - October 7, 1997- St. John's University, Collegeville, MN (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - March 27-30, 1998- Fales Library, Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University, New York, NY, Home of Janet Jurist, New York, NY, The Cornell Club, New York, NY, The Pierpont Morgan Library, New York, NY and The Rosenbach Museum and Library, Philadelphia, PA (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - March 27-30, 1998- Fales Library, Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University, New York, NY, Home of Janet Jurist, New York, NY, The Cornell Club, New York, NY, The Pierpont Morgan Library, New York, NY and The Rosenbach Museum and Library, Philadelphia, PA (Box 3, Folder 46 B)
  - November 7-8, 1998- Young Research Library, UCLA, Huntington Library, San Marino, CA, Home of Daniel Singer, Pasadena, CA (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - May 8, 1999 -National Cathedral, Washington, DC, Home of August and Clare Imholtz, Beltsville, MD, and home of Barbara Mall, Columbia, MD. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - October 23-24, 1999 - Fisher Library, University of Toronto, Art Gallery of Toronto, Toronto, Canada (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - April 15, 2000 - Cornell Club, New York, NY. (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - October 28, 2000- Harry Ransom Humanities Research Center, University of Texas at Austin, TX. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - April 21, 2001- Fales Library, Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University, New York, NY. (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - October 27, 2001- Walt Disney Studios, Burbank, CA and the home of Daniel Singer, Pasadena, CA. (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - April 13, 2002- Princeton University, Princeton, NJ. (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - November 2, 2002- San Francisco Museum of Art, Cartoon Art Museum, San Francisco, CA, and home of Mark and Lisa Burstein, Mill Valley, CA (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - April 12, 2003- Newberry Library, Chicago, IL, and home of Joeland Deborah Birenbaum, Lisle, IL (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Miscellaneous Meeting Correspondence, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Series V: Executive and Publications Committee Meetings
  Files generally consist of notes taken by the Secretary, President, the Publications Director, or August Imholtz, Jr. acting as Recording Secretary. Some files also contain a treasurer's report as well.
  - March 7, 1974- Publications Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - May 11, 1974- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - December 7, 1974- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - May 3, 1975- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - November 1, 1975- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - May 15, 1975- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - November 6, 1976- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - May 7, 1977- Publications Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - November 5, 1977- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - May 13, 1978- Publications Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - October 29, 1983- Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - April 8, 1984- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - April 20, 1985- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - October 15, 1988- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - October 5, 1991- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - May 2, 1991- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - October 17, 1992-Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - May 15, 1993-Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - November 20, 1993- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - June 11, 1994- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - November 12, 1994- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - April 22, 1995-Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - October 28, 1995-Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - April 27, 1996 -Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - November 9, 1996-Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - April 27, 1997- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - October 17, 1997-Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - March 28, 1998-Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - November 8, 1998-Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - May 9, 1999- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - October 23, 1999- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - April 15, 2000- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - October 27, 2000- Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - April 21, 2001- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - October 26, 2001- Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - April 13, 2002- Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - February 27, 2002- Publications Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - November 1, 2002- Executive Committee Meeting, plus Treasurer's Report (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - April 12, 2003- Publications and Executive Committee Meeting (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Series VI: Financial Records
  Financial records and correspondence- some duplicate information noted in Treasurer's Reports
  - Subseries A: Financial Records 1980-1991
    - Financial Records 1980-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Financial Records 1980-1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Financial Records 1991-1999
    - Financial Records 1991-1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous Financial Correspondence 1991-1992
    - Financial Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1-9)
- Series VII: Miscellanous Records
  Contains photographs, offprints, donations, and other items.
  - Subseries A: Photographs from Selected Meetings and Events
    - Photographs, Christ Church, Oxford, July 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Photographs, Christ Church, Oxford, July 1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Photographs, Christ Church, Oxford, July 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, Christ Church, Oxford, July 1982- Janet Jurist copies (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, Westminster Abbey, December 17, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, Winston-Salem, June, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, Home of Alan and Alison Tannenbaum, October 2000. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, Princeton, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      1 compact disc- 12x compatible, CD recordable-Brand name "Mr. Data", 80 minute 700MB capacity. Title: LCSNA Princeton Note: 2002 Photos(both notations written with marker). CD encased in a paper sleeve with plastic viewing window.
  - Subseries B: Audio Tapes of Early Meetings
    Conditions Governing Access
    Audio tapes have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
    - Audiocassette of Early Meeting, "Meeting of LC Society, December 7, 1974" - writing on label in pen. (Box 3, Folder 1)
      148.0001, Audiocassette, C-120, Concertape.
    - Audiocassette of Early Meeting, "LC Meeting, May 15, 1976" - writing on label in pen. (Box 3, Folder 1)
      148.0002, Audiocassette, C-120, Concertape.
    - Audiocassette of Early Meeting, "LC Society, November 1976" - writing on label in pen. (Box 3, Folder 3)
      148.0003, Audiocassette, C-90, Concertape.
  - Subseries C: LCSNA Auction Records
    - LCSNA Auction Records, October 15, 1998- Philadelphia (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - LCSNA Auction Records, October 17, 1990- Baltimore, MD (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - LCSNA Auction Records, June 11, 1994- Winston-Salem, NC (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Subseries D: Stan Marx Memorial Program
    - Stan Marx Memorial Program, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)